hitthedeals.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy | Hit The Deals | UAE - Go Deal Crazy

**Privacy Policy, Refunds &  
Terms & Conditions**

“WIRED Commercial Brokers LLC - [www.hitthedeals.com](http://www.hitthedeals.com/)”  
will be referred to as “HTD”, “us” or “we” in the following Privacy Policy,  
Refunds and Terms & Conditions on this page.

**Please read the following  
carefully to understand & agree on the HTD Privacy Policy, Refund and Terms  
& Conditions. By visiting HTD you agree to the HTD Privacy Policy, Refund  
and Terms & Conditions written on this page. If you do not wish to accept any  
of these you are free to leave the HTD page and not return until you think you  
accept to do so.**

Upon registration we collect your personal information as entered &  
confirmed by you to be true. Your personal information is stored by HTD for the  
purpose of sending email about the daily deals that HTD brings to its  
subscribers, and also to confirm/verify the process of payments for the  
vouchers purchased by the subscriber/user at HTD.

Your personal information is safe with HTD, and we will not disclose  
any subscriber/user information with any Third Party that is not affiliated or  
partners/merchants of HTD.

Your personal information will also be used to better understand the  
requirement of HTD & its’ subscribers/users in order to bring you the best  
deals in town.

**Requirement & Information**

**Age  
Requirement** – HTD Users/Subscribers are only eligible to  
register/subscribe/transact at HTD if they are 18 years of age & above.  
**Personal  
Information, Email & Privacy Policy** \- Upon registration we collect  
your personal information as entered & confirmed by you to be true. Your  
personal information is stored by HTD for the purpose of sending email about  
the daily deals that HTD brings to its subscribers, and also to confirm/verify  
the process of payments for the vouchers purchased by the subscriber/user at  
HTD. Upon registration you will receive emails from HTD about HTD Daily Deals,  
Newsletters, marketing emails on behalf of HTD merchant promotions &  
events. Your personal information is safe with HTD, and we will not disclose  
any subscriber/user information with any Third Party that is not affiliated or  
in business with HTD. Your personal information will also be used to better  
understand the requirement of HTD & its’ subscribers/users in order to  
bring you the best deals in town. The user/subscriber can unsubscribe from such  
emails at any time from the links provided within the email, to stop receiving  
any further emails which may take up to 2-3 working days to be in effect.  
**Legal  
Disclaimer** – We reserve the right to disclose your personal information  
as required by law and when required to protect the HTD rights, protect the  
safety & security of other users/subscribers to comply with a judicial  
proceeding, court order, or legal process served on HTD.  
**Links**  
– HTD contains links to other websites. Please be aware that HTD is not  
responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our  
users/subscribers to be aware when they leave HTD and read the privacy statements  
of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.  
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by HTD.  
**Policy  
Amendment** – HTD has the right to amend the Terms & Conditions and  
its policy on this page at any time which will be effective at the same time of  
amendment, and will accordingly inform the Users/Subscribers on the main page  
of HTD or via an email.  
**Fees  
& Charges** – There is no fees charged to subscribe/register at HTD,  
except for the purchase of vouchers through Credit/Debit Card.  
**User  
Equipment** – User/Subscriber shall be wholly and solely responsible for  
their equipment & charges related to those equipment used to access HTD.  
HTD will not be responsible for any damage or loss to the User/Subscriber’s  
equipment resulting from the use of HTD.  
**Copyright  
& Trademarks** \- Everything located on or in HTD, including the  
Microsites, is the exclusive property of HTD or used with express permission of  
the copyright and/or trademark owner.

Any copying, distributing, transmitting, posting, linking,  
deep linking, or otherwise modifying of HTD or any of the Microsites without  
the express written permission of HTD is strictly prohibited.

Trademarks & Logos displayed at HTD are a trade mark of  
HTD, which is either produced/developed by HTD &/or its partners/businesses  
that are promoted at HTD. Any unauthorized use of the content of this website  
or violation of this policy may result in a copyright, trademark or other  
intellectual property right infringement that may subject you to civil and/or  
criminal penalties.  
**SSL**  
– HTD is a secured website using an SSL (Secured Socket Layer) & a secure  
payment gateway to ensure that your personal & sensitive information is  
safe as it is transmitted to us through an encryption. Unfortunately, no data  
over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  
But we do best to take all security measures to its maximum to avoid any such  
loss of information.  
**Refunds**  
– We always want our customers to be happy. But HTD is not responsible for any  
quality of product or service from the merchant. There is no refund on any  
vouchers purchased, unless the merchant refuses to accept any valid voucher.  
Invalid/Expired vouchers are non-refundable, and no voucher is valid for  
exchange of cash.  
**Credit/Debit  
Card Usage** – Please ensure that the purchase of vouchers through  
Credit/Debit Card is with your own Credit/Debit Card using your own HTD  
account, and not a Third Party Credit/Debit Card and/or a Third Party HTD  
account. Any purchase that is done through a Third Party Credit/Debit Card  
and/or a Third Party HTD account, will entail to invalidation of a voucher  
purchased through that Account/Card at any time, and no refunds will be offered  
by HTD.  
**Cash  
On Delivery** – Cash on Delivery is not available at the time, but will  
be introduced soon.  
**Support**  
– For any further queries or clarifications please send us an email at [support@hitthedeals.com](mailto:support@hitthedeals.com)
